JIAN XIANG (CHAD) ZHAO

 $\frac{647\text{-}262\text{-}2497 \mid \underline{chadzhao1@gmail.com}}{\text{LinkedIn: Jian Xiang (Chad) Zhao} \mid 2A \ Computer \ Engineering}$

SUMMARY OF SKILLS

Languages with Extensive Experience: Python, Java, C++

Languages with Working Knowledge: Bash Scripting, SQL, HTML/CSS, Javascript **Development Tools**: Android Studio, Visual Studio, Vscode, IntelliJ, Selenium WebDriver

Aglile Software: Git/Github, JIRA, Jenkins **Common Programs**: MS Office Suite, LaTex

Other Skills: PC Assembly, Windows Command Line, Agile Team Experience

General knowledge about computer hardware, PC components, PC hardware industry standards

EXPERIENCE

Automation Developer

September 2020 – January 2021

Waterloo, ON

Ford Motor Company Canada

• Developed software tools to automate the testing of vehicle ECU software on actual target devices

- Maintained stability and health of various build projects using CI tool Jenkins
- Debugged on-target ECU software using a command line interface

Developer January 2020 – May 2020

Grand and Toy Vaughan, ON

- Developed automation testing framework for the e-commerce website using Python and Selenium WebDriver
 Scripted complex test cases into automation scripts, freeing up manual testing time
- Achieved increased QA efficiency by deploying automatically generated testing report

Programmer September 2015 – September 2018

FIRST Robotics Thornhill, ON

- Programmed robot using LabView software to complete autonomous operation in competitions
- Built part of robot using power tools, acquiring hands on workshop skills

PROJECTS

StarCraft 2 Game AI

Python, *pysc2*, *python-sc2*

- Achieved scripted autonomous gameplay, now working on developing reinforcement learning
- The agent outperforms a standard built-in game AI

Discord Bot

Python, discord.py

- Retrieves and displays information from integrating with third-party python APIs
- Used back-end MySQL database server to store relevant data

Student Helper Mobile APP

Java, Android Studio, Emulators

- · Modifiable calendar, to-do list, reminder features that helps students organize activities and manage projects
- Mainly used fragments to combine different functionality

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Applied Science | Computer Engineering

September 2019 - Present 2A Term

University of Waterloo

Waterloo, ON

• Relevant courses: Data Structures and Algorithms (C++), Digital Computers, Numerical Methods (MATLAB)

IB Diploma | Secondary School

September 2015 – June 2019

St Robert Catholic High School

Thornhill, ON